fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
Akamaru Surprised!
Gaara's Exceptional Ability
That guy...?
Everyone hide!
No, lie low quick!
W-Where is that guy?
Naruto...
That fool, he finally woke up.
You are quite one of a kind.
Actually, you are getting on my nerves.
Sakura-chan!
— What?
— Y-Y-Your...!
Sakura-chan... your hair!
Oh! This...?
I'm changing my image,
changing my image!
I like it better long but,
when I move around in
a forest like this,
it gets in the way if it's long.
By the way...
why are you guys here?!
Hah... It's such a pain
to explain it to you.
Everybody helped out.
Huh?
Sakura's putting on a show of bravado...
I'll take care of him from here.
Ah... Okay...
Keep it together! Lee!
Oh? Tenten, why are you here?
I came to help.
Huh...?
Those guys,
where's the Sound Village Ninja?
A kid named Sasuke
drove them away!
Really...
Why did you hastily decide
to act on your own?!
Besides, you really got beaten up!
S-Sakura-san was in danger.
So as a man, I...
You're kidding...!
If it were Lee alone,
he wouldn't have lost to those guys.
You're really stupid.
I can't argue with that.
You, Bushy-Brow!
Naruto!
Don't say rude things to Lee-san!
What in the world...
happened while I was asleep?
That Naruto,
he's completely out of the loop.
He's not the type to be
the protagonist of a story, certainly not.
Lee-san...
Thank you.
Because of you,
I was able to wake up.
I feel like I've gotten a little stronger!
Sakura-san...
It looks like my efforts
weren't enough!
Sasuke-kun... Just what you'd expect
from the Uchiha clan.
To chase off the Sound Village Ninja,
just as I thought,
you possess amazing strength.
I was beaten to a pulp.
What?! He was beaten to a pulp?!
What's he talking about?
Were those guys really that strong?
Sakura-san!
The Lotus of Leaf Village
blooms twice.
Huh?
When we meet again,
I will have become a stronger man.
I pledge it.
Okay.
Hey, Sakura!
Come here, come here!
Your hair! I'll fix it for you!
That'd be great.
You are really sneaky.
Hugging him like that,
you little billboard brow.
It's called first come-first served,
Miss Ino Pig.
Uchiha... Sasuke.
At any rate... he's a strong opponent.
Are you okay, Akamaru?
Is he still shaking?
It's already been half a day.
Akamaru...
I don't blame him,
it's because he saw that thing...
After all, brains are most important
in survival!
Right. Akamaru?
Lucky for us,
the guys who got caught in
the trap had an earth scroll!
We'll be the first to
the tower at this rate!
Don't get carried away.
That's dangerous.
No matter how small a bug it is,
it has to guard itself at all times.
We have to pay attention to avoid
coming across any enemies...
This is safety.
I know that!
As always, you're speaking in a way
that's difficult to understand, bug-nerd.
Um... B-But...
What Shino-kun said...
He has a point.
I know! C'mon.
Naruto-kun...
I hope nothing's happened to him...
Hey you two, stop.
We're being careful not to
come across enemy, right?
Then Hinata!
Can you see 1 kilometer
in that direction?
Yep... I'll have a look.
Byakugan!
T-There's someone there.
Evidently there are... 6 people...
Okay! Let's go look!
Huh?
Kiba! What are you saying?
We're not doing that.
The Proctor told us to bring
one of each "Heaven" and "Earth"
scroll in a pair.
He didn't say not to
take more than that.
If we take more, that means
some other teams will be left out.
B-But...
We'll just see what's going on at first..
If it looks too dangerous,
we won't battle for no reason.
— Let's go!
— Oh!
He's an irritating type, that one.
What's up, Akamaru?
What happened? You stopped suddenly.
Akamaru suddenly got frightened.
W-Why is that?
Akamaru can sniff out the level of enemy's
Chakra and tell his strength.
But this is the first time I've
seen him this scared.
The people going at it up ahead
aren't ordinary guys...
Sand Village kids coming
to challenge us forthright.
It's foolish.
What's that little guy thinking
to get involved with those guys...?!
W-What is Akamaru saying...?
He's saying that big guy is dangerous.
T-They certainly look like bad news...
They seem really strong.
Hey, kids, you should
pick your opponents...
You're all going to die.
That's enough of you.
Let's do this quickly...
old man from Hidden Rain Village.
Which scroll do those guys have...
Hey, Gaara!
Doesn't it make sense to
follow them
and gather information
before hunting them?
If they have the same type of scroll
there's no need to fight.
Unnecessary battles are-
It doesn't matter.
If their eyes meet with mine...
I'll kill them all.
That's why I don't want
to be with this guy.
Well, let's do it. Quickly!
Die, kid!
Ninja Art: Senbon Rainstorm!
Hidden Senbons!
Up, down, right, left,
there is no dead spot in this Jutsu.
In addition, all the Senbons are
controlled by my Chakra
and attack on the intended prey!
Too easy.
Is that all?
I-It can't be...?!
Not even one...?
No wounds...? Ridiculous!
Senbon Rainstorm, huh...?
Well, I'll make it rain blood.
What a giant Chakra.
And, that sand...
It smells terrible.
Smell?
A strong smell of blood...
Wall of sand...?
That's right.
An absolute defense by sand!
He manipulates sand inside
a gourd and
hardens it with magnified Chakra.
It defends the circumference
of Gaara's body.
It's a Jutsu that only
he can get away with...
Furthermore, it's somehow always
automatically done
without Gaara's intentions.
Which means that all attacks
in front of Gaara fade into nothing.
That little...
You guys can't defeat our Gaara.
Don't underestimate me!
This guy's a goner...
That's what you get for rebelling
against Gaara...
Sand Coffin!
I can't move...
T-This won't...!
I can cover your loud mouth
and kill you.
But that's too pathetic.
Sand Burial!
There's no pain.
I knocked him even harder
than was necessary.
The bloody tears of a corpse merge
with vast sinking sand
and provide more power
to the demon of war.
T-The scroll.
We'll give it to you!
Please! Let us go!
No!
T-This is bad.
Let's escape quickly!
If he finds us he'll kill us!
Luckily it is a Heaven scroll.
Okay! Let's go to the tower.
Shut up.
It's still... not enough for me!
U-Uh-oh! Did he notice us?!
Let's quit... Gaara.
Are you scared, coward?
Gaara! It's certainly no problem for you,
but it's too dangerous for us!
One set of scrolls is good.
More than this is...
Lame people don't give directions to me.
That's enough!
How about if you sometimes listen
to what your older brother has to say?!
I've never thought of you as my siblings.
If you get in my way... I'll kill you.
G-Gaara cut it out! Please.
Don't say something so cold.
As a favor to your sister... Okay?!
Gaara!
Fine.
That's why I hate brats.
What? So that's it Akamaru?
C'mon, you should have
said something sooner.
Nobody's here...?
Heh heh! We're the first?!
No, I sensed someone a little while ago.
More importantly, is Akamaru okay?
He's been scared ever since then.
Now that you mention it,
what did Akamaru say before?
Oh... Akamaru said that it
was dangerous
because that sand squirt
would kill that big guy.
Sheesh! Just like I thought,
there's no other place to go!
They've already made us
wait for half a day!
How much longer do we have to wait?
Anyway. That Sand Village squirt...
I don't know what he is but,
that guy...
He's too dangerous.
It's becoming a real disaster,
but we can't cancel this test.
What do you mean?
Excuse me!
What is it?!
We're talking about something important!
Excuse me.
But... Uh...
Please take a look at this!
The video...?
Ready? Here! Look at the time!
T-This is...
It's a recording inside the tower,
one hour and thirty-seven minutes
after the start of the second test!
Three Shinobi from Hidden Sand Village
broke through the second test.
This can't be...!
In a mere ninety-seven minutes...
This has never happened!
This is an anomaly.
Those guys are not Genin level.
They've rewritten the
fastest time by four hours...
It's not just that.
What do you mean?
It's 10 kilometers
from the test entrances to the tower.
Ferocious animals, poisonous insects,
the rugged forest road...
As if those were not there...
Especially the brown-haired kid
right in front...
What about him?
You don't notice?
I see. This is quite a surprise.
What about him is so...?
Look closely at his body.
I see.
He doesn't have a single scratch.
What's worse, there's not
a smudge of dirt on his clothing.
Even I...
No, any of the other Chunin...
It's impossible for us to
make it to this tower without a scratch.
It's likely that it has something
to do with his ability.
After a long time, a dependable
guy has appeared.
Even though he's got evil eyes.
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
— Please!
— No!
— Just a little bit.
— Really only a little bit.
— No means no!
I'll just look a little and put it back.
Remember what the
Proctors said, useless.
When they say don't look, don't look,
it just makes me want
to look all the more!
If you can look when you can,
let's look!
Naruto lost it!
Sakura! Get a hold of Naruto!
Next episode:
"Absolutely No Peeking! The Secret of the Scroll."
I really want to look!